( overlapping chatter, yelling )
♪
( Johnny Black giggles )
( Kirito gasps ) ASUNA!
WATCH OUT!
( Asuna gasps )
Kirito: RUN! GET OUTTA HERE!
- ( hypodermic hisses )
- ( Asuna gasps )
( gasps )
( Kirito grunts )
Asuna: KIRITO!
( shuddering )
♪
( running footsteps )
( Suguha panting )
ASUNA!
Asuna: MRS. KIRIGAYA.
SUGUHA.
( all gasp )
( ventilator hissing )
Doctor: HE’S STABLE
AND OUT OF DANGER NOW.
Midori: THANK GOODNESS.
Doctor: THAT SAID,
HIS HEART DID STOP
FOR MORE THAN FIVE MINUTES,
SO THERE’S A STRONG CHANCE
HE’S SUFFERED
SOME DEGREE OF BRAIN DAMAGE.
( both gasp )
NOW, WE DON’T KNOW
ANYTHING FOR SURE YET,
BUT IT’S POSSIBLE
HE COULD HAVE
A PERMANENT MENTAL
AND/OR PHYSICAL DISABILITY
OR, WORST CASE,
HE NEVER REGAINS CONSCIOUSNESS.
- ( Asuna gasps )
- Suguha: NO!
Doctor: UNTIL HE HAS AN MRI,
WE WON’T KNOW THE SCOPE
OF THE DAMAGE, IF THERE IS ANY.
HE’LL HAVE TO BE TRANSFERRED
TO A BETTER EQUIPPED FACILITY
FOR THAT.
IF YOU FOLLOW ME, I CAN GET YOU
STARTED ON THE PAPERWORK.
Midori: OKAY.
( Asuna shudders )
Kikuoka: HELLO, ASUNA. SUGUHA.
Asuna: MR. KIKUOKA.
Kikuoka:
ARE KIRITO’S PARENTS HERE?
I’D LIKE A WORD.
♪
♪ SHINY SWORD, MY DIAMOND ♪
( singing in Japanese )
♪ IT’S TIME ♪
♪
Suguha: SORRY I’M LATE!
Asuna: ISN’T YOUR MOM COMING?
Suguha: SHE’S STILL TRYING
TO FIND A PARKING SPOT.
SHE WANTS US TO SIGN IN
AND WAIT FOR HER IN THE LOBBY.
Asuna: OKAY.
I HOPE THEY CAN HELP HIM.
DO YOU KNOW
IF HE’S HERE ALREADY?
Suguha: YEAH.
THE NURSE ON THE PHONE
SAID THEY BROUGHT HIM OVER
EARLIER TODAY.
Kikuoka: THERE’S ONLY
ONE HOSPITAL IN THE WORLD
THAT HAS THE RIGHT EQUIPMENT.
IF HE GOES THERE, KAZUTO WILL
HAVE THE BEST TREATMENT.
Asuna: HI. WE’RE HERE
TO VISIT A PATIENT.
Receptionist: "KAZUTO KIRIGAYA."
ONE MOMENT,
AND I’LL LOOK HIM UP.
- UH...
- Asuna: HUH?
Receptionist: UM, I’M SORRY.
I HAVE TO CHECK
WITH MY SUPERVISOR.
PLEASE WAIT HERE.
Lisbeth: WHY WOULDN’T
THEY LET YOU SEE HIM?
Asuna: THEY SAID IT HAS TO DO
WITH THE EQUIPMENT
THEY’RE USING.
HE CAN’T HAVE VISITORS
UNTIL HE’S RECOVERED.
Silica: BUT THEY CAN’T DO THAT.
THAT’S TOTALLY ILLEGAL.
YOU’RE FAMILY.
HOSPITALS CAN’T KEEP A PATIENT’S
FAMILY FROM VISITING.
Sinon: SHE’S RIGHT.
THIS SOUNDS FISHY.
Asuna: YES, IT DOES,
SO WE DUG AROUND TO SEE
IF WE COULD FIND ANYTHING.
Suguha: THE HOSPITAL RECORDS SAY
HE’S REGISTERED AS A PATIENT,
BUT THEN I NOTICED
SOMETHING THAT DIDN’T MESH.
THE AMBULANCE TRANSPORTING HIM
NEVER STOPPED THERE.
Silica: THAT DOESN’T
MAKE ANY SENSE.
IF THEY DIDN’T TAKE HIM THERE,
THEN WHERE DID THEY?
Sinon: WHAT DOES KIKUOKA
HAVE TO SAY ABOUT THIS?
Asuna: HE HASN’T RETURNED
ANY OF MY CALLS OR MY EMAILS,
AND THE MINISTRY SAID
HE’S BEEN OUT SINCE YESTERDAY
ON BUSINESS.
Lisbeth: I BET. THAT CREEP’S
TOTALLY AVOIDING YOU!
NO MATTER HOW YOU SLICE IT,
HE’S UP TO SOMETHING SUSPICIOUS.
Sinon: YEAH,
BUT THE QUESTION IS, WHAT?
I DON’T TRUST HIM.
FOR ALL WE KNOW,
HE COULD BE MAKING KIRITO
DO SOME KIND
OF WEIRD V.R. EXPERIMENT.
Silica: BUT HOW? KIRITO CAN’T
DO ANYTHING IF HE’S UNCONSCIOUS.
Sinon: MAYBE HE CAN, THOUGH.
WHAT I MEAN IS, SURE,
KIRITO’S BODY
CAN’T DO ANYTHING NOW,
BUT THAT DOESN’T MATTER,
SINCE THEY HAVE A RIG
THAT CAN ACCESS HIS SOUL.
( Asuna gasps )
THE SOUL TRANSLATOR.
Sinon: MM-HMM.
Silica:
WHAT’S A SOUL TRANSLATOR?
Lisbeth: I NEVER HEARD OF IT.
Asuna: IT’S A NEW
FULL-DIVE MACHINE
THAT CAN ACCESS AND INTERFACE
WITH HUMAN SOULS.
A COMPANY CALLED RATH
IS THE ONE DEVELOPING IT.
Suguha: WHOA, HANG ON. RATH?
THOSE ARE THE PEOPLE KAZUTO
HAS BEEN WORKING PART-TIME FOR.
Asuna: DID HE TELL YOU
ANYTHING ABOUT THEM?
Suguha: NO.
NOTHING SPECIFIC, REALLY.
HE DID SAY THEY WERE
BASED IN ROPPONGI,
BUT THAT’S ABOUT IT.
Sinon: OKAY,
IF THAT’S WHERE THEY ARE,
THAT’S WHERE
WE SHOULD START LOOKING.
Asuna: ACTUALLY THERE MIGHT BE
ANOTHER WAY
TO TRACK KIRITO’S LOCATION.
IT’S KIND OF
A LONG SHOT, THOUGH.
Sinon: WHAT IS IT?
Asuna: I TOLD YOU ABOUT IT
THE OTHER DAY, REMEMBER?
THE APP HE MADE, THIS THING.
Sinon: OH! RIGHT,
HIS LITTLE HEART MONITOR.
Silica: WAIT. WHAT?
HEART MONITOR?
Asuna: I LOST THE SIGNAL TO HIM
A WHILE AGO,
BUT I HAVE SOMEONE TRACING
HIS LAST KNOWN COORDINATES NOW.
Sinon: WHO?
Asuna: HEY, YUI, YOU THERE?
Yui: YES!
I JUST FINISHED ANALYZING
ALL THE DATA.
I’LL TRACK THE COORDINATES
FROM DADDY’S BIO-MONITOR NOW.
THIS ONE IS THE PLACE
WHERE DADDY STARTED,
SETAGAYA GENERAL HOSPITAL.
THIS ONE IS THE FIRST LOCATION
DADDY’S MONITOR
PINGED A CELL TOWER,
AOBADAI BLOCK THREE,
MEGURO WARD.
THE TIME STAMP IS 20:50
ON JUNE 29, 2026.
HERE IS DADDY’S
PREDICTED ROUTE.
THE NEXT TIME HE PINGED
WAS HERE,
SHIROKANEDAI BLOCK ONE,
MINATO WARD, AT 21:10.
AND LAST...
HE PINGED AGAIN
AT KAIGAN BLOCK TWO,
MINATO WARD, AT 21:20.
AND THAT’S IT.
I CHECKED ALL THE PACKETS,
THERE HAVE BEEN
NO FURTHER PINGS.
Suguha: HE’S NOT
IN TOKOROZAWA OR ROPPONGI.
Asuna: YUI, WHAT’S
AT THAT LAST ADDRESS YOU HAVE?
Yui: ALL I CAN TELL IS THAT
IT IS SOME SORT OF WAREHOUSE.
Sinon: WHY WOULD THEY
TAKE HIM OUT THERE?
( Asuna gasps )
MINATO WARD.
( stereo playing music )
( singing in Japanese )
Klein: ALMOST THERE.
THIS TIME OF NIGHT,
THERE AIN’T TOO MUCH TRAFFIC
HEADIN’ THIS WAY.
Asuna: THANKS, KLEIN.
I REALLY APPRECIATE
YOU DRIVING US OUT HERE.
Klein: AH, COME ON.
QUIT THANKIN’ ME.
I’D DO ANYTHING FOR YOU GUYS.
CAN’T BELIEVE WE WERE ALL HAVING
FUN IN "GGO" THE OTHER DAY,
AND NOW...
WELL, I JUST HOPE HE’S OKAY.
Suguha: I JUST HOPE
HE STOPS GETTING MIXED UP
IN WEIRD EXPERIMENTS
AFTER THIS.
Klein: DIDN’T YOU GUYS SAY
THIS RATH COMPANY
WAS IN ROPPONGI?
SHOULDN’T WE BE
LOOKING FOR HIM THERE, TOO?
Suguha: ACTUALLY...
SINON AND THE OTHERS
SHOULD BE THERE BY NOW.
Asuna: IT’S SO WEIRD.
THERE’S NO INFO ON RATH AT ALL.
YUI CHECKED ALL
THE PUBLIC RECORDS, EVERYTHING.
ALL SHE FOUND
WAS THEIR ADDRESS.
THERE WAS NOTHING ABOUT
THE COMPANY OR WHAT THEY DID.
Suguha: THE SAME WITH
THAT SOUL TRANSLATOR THING.
IF IT’S NEW TECH,
NO ONE’S TALKING ABOUT IT.
WE COULDN’T FIND PATENT
APPLICATIONS OR COPYRIGHTS.
Klein: A MACHINE THAT
CAN INTERFACE WITH THE SOUL
IS THE BIGGEST DEAL EVER.
YOU KNOW
WHO DOESN’T PATENT THAT?
SNEAKY BASTARDS, THAT’S WHO.
OH, COOL! WE’RE ALMOST THERE.
THAT’S IT, HUH?
I DON’T GET IT. WHAT’S THE POINT
OF STASHING KIRI-DUDE
OUT HERE BY THE DOCKS?
- ( cell phone buzzing )
- ( Asuna stammers )
HEY, LIZ.
Lisbeth: WE’RE OUT IN FRONT
OF RATH’S OFFICE NOW.
THEIR SECURITY’S SUPER TIGHT,
AND THEY WOULDN’T
TELL US A THING.
OH, AND THERE’S
CAMERAS ALL AROUND,
SO WE ASKED YUI
TO CHECK OUT THE FOOTAGE.
AS FAR AS SHE COULD TELL,
THEY DIDN’T BRING KIRITO HERE.
Asuna: OKAY.
I’LL CALL YOU LATER.
HEY, YUI.
Yui: HERE, MOMMY.
I JUST CHECKED ALL THE SECURITY
CAMERAS IN THE HARBOR.
THIS PROPERTY HAS
A HELIPAD OVER THERE.
YESTERDAY, AT 21:20,
A HELICOPTER TOOK OFF FROM IT.
Asuna: DO YOU KNOW
IF HE WAS ON IT?
Yui: WELL, I CAN’T CONFIRM,
BUT I BELIEVE HE WAS.
( Suguha gasps ) OH, MY GOD.
THEY COULD HAVE TAKEN HIM
ANYWHERE THEN. NOW WHAT?
Asuna:
WAIT. LET’S NOT PANIC.
YUI.
JUST CONFIRMING,
THIS IS THE LAST PLACE
HIS SIGNAL SHOWED UP?
Yui: YES, IT IS.
Asuna: HE NEEDS TREATMENT,
SO THEY’LL HAVE TO TAKE HIM
TO SOME KIND OF FACILITY.
BUT IF THEY LANDED,
KIRITO’S SIGNAL SHOULD HAVE
POPPED UP AGAIN BY NOW,
UNLESS WHEREVER HE IS
IS OUT OF RANGE.
Yui: YES, THAT MUST BE THE CASE.
IT’S POSSIBLE THEY TOOK HIM
OUT OF THE COUNTRY.
Klein: SAY WHAT?!
Yui: IT’S ONE POSSIBILITY.
IT’S ALSO THE MOST LIKELY.
Klein: WHAT DO WE DO?
HE COULD BE ANYWHERE
IN THE WORLD BY NOW.
Suguha: HE’S RIGHT. HOW THE HECK
ARE WE GONNA FIND HIM?
Asuna: KIRITO.
Yui: CHEER UP, MOMMY. HAVE HOPE.
Asuna: I’M TRYING.
Yui: WHEN YOU
WERE TRAPPED IN ALFHEIM,
DADDY SEARCHED
ALL OVER FOR YOU.
HE NEVER GAVE UP,
AND EVENTUALLY, HE FOUND YOU!
Asuna: I KNOW.
Yui: THEN CHEER UP!
NOW IT’S YOUR TURN
TO SEARCH FOR HIM!
I KNOW YOU’LL FIND A CLUE
THAT WILL LEAD YOU
STRAIGHT TO DADDY.
AND IF ANYONE STANDS
IN YOUR WAY, THEY’LL BE SORRY.
BECAUSE NOTHING, NO ONE,
CAN SEVER THE BOND BETWEEN YOU.
♪
Asuna: IT DIDN’T MATTER
WHAT DANGERS HE FACED.
KIRITO NEVER BACKED DOWN.
I’LL FIND HIM,
IF IT’S THE LAST THING I DO.
THANKS FOR THE PEP TALK, YUI.
YOU’RE RIGHT. I WON’T GIVE UP.
( Yui giggles )
THAT’S THE SPIRIT!
Asuna: LET’S THINK
FOR A SEC HERE.
WHAT DO WE KNOW ABOUT RATH?
ASSUMING THEY’RE THE ONES
WHO HAVE KIRITO NOW.
SUGUHA, DID KIRITO EVER
TELL YOU ANYTHING ABOUT THEM,
ANYTHING AT ALL?
Suguha: I HAVEN’T
SEEN HIM THAT MUCH LATELY
’CAUSE OF HIS WORK.
WE TALKED A BIT
NOW AND THEN, BUT NOT MUCH.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
COME TO THINK OF IT,
HE DID SAY SOMETHING ONCE,
SOMETHING ABOUT
HOW THAT MACHINE HE WAS TESTING
WAS BASED ON THE MEDICUBOID.
Asuna: THEY SHARE THE SAME TECH?
I HAD NO IDEA.
THE MEDICUBOID.
I JUST REMEMBERED
SOMETHING HE TOLD ME.
YOU KNOW
WHO DESIGNED THE MEDICUBOID?
THE COMMANDER, AKIHIKO KAYABA.
HE LAID THE GROUNDWORK,
BUT HIS PARTNER DEVELOPED IT
FOR HOSPITALS.
Kirito: YEAH, IN FACT,
SHE WAS TAKING CARE
OF HEATHCLIFF’S BODY
WHILE HE WAS DIVING.
SHE WAS HIS HEAD RESEARCHER.
SHE HELPED HIM DEVELOP
FULL-DIVE TECHNOLOGY.
Asuna: WHAT WAS HER NAME?
RINKO KOJIRO, I THINK.
Yui: I’LL RUN A SEARCH.
I FOUND SOMEONE WHO’S MOST
LIKELY THE PERSON YOU MENTIONED.
CURRENTLY, SHE’S A RESEARCHER
AT THE CALIFORNIA
TECHNOLOGICAL INSTITUTE.
THIS IS HER.
THE UNIVERSITY’S DATABASE
DETAILS HER CAREER SO FAR.
SHE’S A FORMER MEMBER
OF THE SHIGEMURA LAB
AT TOTO INSTITUTE
OF TECHNOLOGY’S
DEPARTMENT OF ELECTRICAL
AND ELECTRONIC ENGINEERING.
Suguha: WAIT. ISN’T SHIGEMURA
THE GUY WHO MADE THE AUGMA?
Asuna: YEAH, AND KAYABA
WAS ONE OF HIS STUDENTS.
SHE MIGHT KNOW SOMETHING
ABOUT THE S.T.L. AND RATH.
( Rinko sighs )
WAIT. A FLOATING CASTLE?
Kayaba: YEAH. A CASTLE
IN THE SKY WITH NUMEROUS FLOORS,
100 FLOORS, MAYBE,
AND EACH ONE HAS A TOWN,
A FOREST, AND A PLAIN.
TO GET TO THE NEXT FLOOR,
YOU CLIMB A LONG STAIRCASE,
AND WHEN YOU REACH THE TOP,
YOU’LL FIND A PALACE.
Rinko: SO WHAT’S IN THE PALACE?
Kayaba: I DON’T KNOW.
WHEN I WAS YOUNG,
I USED TO GO TO THAT CASTLE
EVERY NIGHT IN MY DREAMS.
EVERY NIGHT,
I’D CLIMB UP EACH STAIRCASE
AND GET CLOSER TO THE TOP,
BIT BY BIT.
BUT THEN, AT SOME POINT,
( sighs )
I WASN’T ABLE TO GO THERE AGAIN.
IT WAS JUST A SILLY DREAM.
I PRETTY MUCH FORGOT
ALL ABOUT IT.
Rinko: LIAR.
( computer chimes )
NOT AGAIN.
HMM?
ASUNA YUUKI?
Pilot: ALMOST THERE.
YOU’LL SEE THE OCEAN TURTLE
IN A SEC.
♪
Rinko: WHY "TURTLE"?
OH, SEE IT.
YEAH, I GUESS IT LOOKS LIKE ONE.
LOOKS MORE LIKE A PIG
FROM HERE, THOUGH.
OR A PIG-TURTLE.
WASN’T THERE
A CREATURE LIKE THAT
IN THE "ALICE IN WONDERLAND"
BOOK?
Woman: RATH.
Man: DR. KOJIRO. WELCOME ABOARD.
AND WHO THIS IS?
Rinko: THIS IS MY ASSISTANT,
MAYUMI REYNOLDS.
Mayumi: IT’S NICE TO MEET YOU.
Nakanishi: LIKEWISE.
MY NAME IS LIEUTENANT NAKANISHI.
I’LL ESCORT YOU BELOW DECK.
THIS WAY. WATCH YOUR STEP.
I NEED YOU TO VERIFY DR. KOJIRO
AND HER ASSISTANT, MS. REYNOLDS,
FOR ACCESS TO SECTOR S-3.
Guard: RIGHT AWAY, SIR.
I.D. VERIFIED.
I’M SORRY, MA’AM.
YOU’LL HAVE TO REMOVE
YOUR SUNGLASSES FOR THIS.
Mayumi: SURE.
Guard: I.D. VERIFIED. PROCEED.
( Rinko sighs )
SECURITY’S AWFULLY TIGHT HERE.
YOU’D THINK THE MIDDLE
OF THE OCEAN WAS SAFE.
Nakanishi:
ACTUALLY, WE’RE REQUIRED
TO RUN FULL-BODY CHECKS
ON GUESTS.
BUT YOU’VE GONE THROUGH
THREE METAL AND EXPLOSIVES
DETECTORS ALREADY, SO...
( Rinko gasps )
Kikuoka:
WELCOME TO RATH, DOCTOR.
( Rinko grunts ) KIKUOKA.
SORRY, LIEUTENANT COLONEL.
YOU LOOK COMFY.
WHERE’S YOUR UNIFORM?
Nakanishi: UM, SIR, I’LL BE
ON THE COMMS IF YOU NEED ME.
Kikuoka:
I’VE BEEN STUCK OUT HERE
IN THE MIDDLE OF THE OCEAN
FOR ABOUT A MONTH NOW.
I CAN’T ALWAYS BE IN A UNIFORM
OR A SUIT FOR THAT MATTER.
- I CAN’T BEGIN TO TELL YOU
- ( sandals clicking )
HOW HAPPY I AM
TO FINALLY HAVE YOU HERE.
I WAS STARTING TO WORRY
MY PERSISTENCE SCARED YOU AWAY.
Rinko: JUST BECAUSE I’M HERE
DOESN’T MEAN
I’VE AGREED TO ANYTHING.
Kikuoka: HMM?
( sighs )
FAIR ENOUGH,
BUT BEFORE YOU DECIDE ANYTHING,
YOU SHOULD KNOW
YOU’RE ONE OF THREE PEOPLE
WHOSE SKILLS ARE CRUCIAL
TO THIS PROJECT,
AND NOW YOU’RE ALL HERE.
Rinko: HMM. CONGRATULATIONS.
WELL, WELL, LOOK WHO IT IS.
DON’T TELL ME HE ROPED YOU IN
ON THIS TOO, HIGA.
Higa: WHAT DO YOU THINK?
OF COURSE HE DID!
HONESTLY, I’M STOKED TO BE HERE.
I’M CARRYING ON THE LEGACY
OF SHIGEMURA LAB.
Rinko: I SWEAR, YOU HAVEN’T
CHANGED A BIT, HAVE YOU?
WELL, WHO’S THE THIRD PERSON
YOU MENTIONED?
Kikuoka: UNFORTUNATELY,
I CAN’T INTRODUCE YOU NOW,
BUT DON’T WORRY.
IN A FEW DAYS, I’LL SHOW--
Asuna: MR. KIKUOKA...
- YOU’LL TAKE US TO HIM NOW.
- ( Kikuoka gasps )
A-ASUNA, I--
WH-WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
Rinko: SHE SENT ME
AN INTERESTING EMAIL.
Asuna: AN ORGANIZATION
CALLED RATH
IS DEVELOPING A MACHINE
CALLED THE SOUL TRANSLATOR.
IT’S BASED ON THE MEDICUBOID,
THE MEDICAL FULL-DIVE RIG
YOU DESIGNED THE TECHNOLOGY FOR.
KAZUTO KIRIGAYA
WAS TESTING THIS NEW MACHINE,
BUT HE DISAPPEARED, AND I
NEED YOUR HELP TO FIND HIM.
Rinko: KAZUTO KIRIGAYA?
Kirito: I WAS
IN THE OLD "S.A.O." SERVER,
AND I MET KAYABA’S
DIGITAL GHOST THERE.
( Rinko gasps )
Kirito: WE SPOKE.
HE GAVE ME A PROGRAM
CALLED THE SEED.
DO YOU KNOW IT? IF YOU DO,
I’D LIKE TO GET YOUR THOUGHTS.
( Rinko sighs )
IF YOU HATE HIM
FOR WHAT HE DID,
THEN JUST DELETE IT,
AND FORGET ALL ABOUT IT.
IT’S OKAY, REALLY. END IT.
BUT IF THERE’S
STILL A PART OF YOU
THAT SEES V.R.’S POTENTIAL...
Asuna: AFTER KIRITO DISAPPEARED,
I WENT THROUGH HIS CONTACTS,
AND THAT’S WHERE
I FOUND YOUR EMAIL.
IF YOU KNOW ANYTHING ABOUT RATH,
ANYTHING AT ALL,
IT COULD HELP ME FIND HIM.
YOU’RE MY LAST HOPE, DR. KOJIRO.
HELP ME, PLEASE.
Rinko: SORRY.
DID WE SURPRISE YOU?
ARE YOU HAVING
SECOND THOUGHTS NOW
ABOUT INVITING ME TO BE
ON YOUR PROJECT, MR. KIKUOKA?
Kikuoka: APPARENTLY,
OUR SECURITY
WASN’T THOROUGH ENOUGH.
I KNOW WE HAVE YOUR ASSISTANT’S
PHOTO FROM THE UNIVERSITY.
THEY SHOULD HAVE RUN
A PROPER CHECK.
Asuna: THEY DID. ON OUR WAY IN,
THEY SCANNED MY FACE
QUITE A FEW TIMES, IN FACT.
BUT I HAD HER ASSISTANT’S PHOTO
IN THE SCHOOL’S DATABASE
SWITCHED WITH MINE A WHILE AGO.
( Kikuoka gasps )
Asuna: I HAPPEN TO KNOW SOMEONE
WHO’S GREAT
AT BUSTING THROUGH FIREWALLS.
Rinko: RIGHT NOW,
THE REAL MAYUMI
IS PROBABLY ON A BEACH
SOMEWHERE WORKING ON HER TAN.
Asuna: TAKE ME TO KIRITO.
♪
( singing in Japanese )
♪ THE IRIS TO YOU ♪